# Operational Manager/Full Stack Web Developer

https://abyykkonen.github.io/annbyykkonen.github.io/

### **SUMMARY OF QUALIFICATIONS**

I'm an extraordinary leader with a deep knowledge of customer service. I have a passion to lead by example and to work side-by-side with my employees. I have over 7 years of experience as a leader and over a decade of experience in customer focused positions. I continue to always grow and improve myself.

I have recently completed my certificate in Full Stack Web Development. I have been working on different projects to help cultivate my skills in HTML, JavaScript, CSS, and React.

#### **PROJECTS**

Expansion of clinic, Add more rooms to clinic

• Developed the renovation strategy and oversaw the \$150,000 clinic remodel while open for business.

# Opening a new clinic, Opened two dental clinics

• Oversaw each one of the \$1 million dollar projects. Helped to keep the projects running smoothly and on schedule for the opening day so we would bew open for business on schedule.

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE:**

Full Stack Web Developer, Autodidact Udemy Student - November 2020 - February 2021

- Solo Project: The Waverly Inn
  - $\circ$  I sought to create a website that was easy for the customers to use.  $\circ$  This project was created with HTML and CSS
- Solo Project: Opal's Design
  - o My goal for this project was to create a central focused project that allowed the customer to see different focal points throughout the website. o This project was created with HTML and CSS. Throughout my process I have learned both the front end and the back end. This process has shown me how to create a website that is appealing to the customers.

#### Practice Manager, White Birch Dental - February 2019 to present

- Lead by example to ensure an exceptional patient experience lead, motivate and manage clinicians and front staff to deliver one of a kind dental care
- Quickly and professionally resolve any patient dissatisfaction
- Responsible for all HR-related tasks managing staffing levels within office needs: interviewing, hiring, firing, training, performance management, and disciplinary actions
- Review financial reports, monitor accounts, and prepare financial forecasts.

Patient service coordinator, Fairview Homecare and Hospice, January 2017 to February 2019

- Continuously communicate and update on staffing needs and operations of all clients
- Utilize independent judgment to problem solve caregiver client, and staffing concerns manage, coordinate and schedule initial triage of information and scheduling requests for the clients
- Provide critical leadership and management support for assigned accounts

### Practice Manager, Metro Dentalcare - August 2011 to January 2017

- Operate as key business partner and liaison to The dentists to develop organizational goals and manage progress through monthly, quarterly, and yearly business reviews
- Review financial reports, monitor accounts, and prepare financial forecasts.
- Establishes good working relationships and collaborative arrangement with clinicians and front staff to help achieve the goals of the organization
- Responsible for all HR-related tasks managing staffing levels within office needs: interviewing, hiring, firing, training, performance management, and disciplinary actions

## **EDUCATION**

Bachelors of Business Administration, Northwestern College, May 2011

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp, November 2020 to February 2021